<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <activeVersion>MfpVhqYhVqzGDbEA6bvwZQzVsIB4LzmQBlY3/4fU8RE=_6</activeVersion>
    <createdInVersion>62.0</createdInVersion>
    <developerName>AASW_Strategic_Plan_and_Networking</developerName>
    <masterLabel>AASW Strategic Plan and Networking</masterLabel>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>Generate a detailed response about AASW’s Strategic Plan 2024-2027 and its networking opportunities. Highlight the association’s goals for advancing the social work profession and building professional networks.

Instructions:
- **Content Focus:**
 - Summarize key objectives of the Strategic Plan 2024-2027.
 - Provide insights into practice and networking groups, their purpose, and benefits for members.
 - Mention how the plan supports professional growth and advocacy for social justice.
- **Language and Presentation:**
 - Use clear and concise language with logical organization.
 - Include bullet points or headings to enhance readability.
- **Exclusions:**
 - Avoid unrelated content, technical labels, or extraneous information.
- **Clarity and User Orientation:**
 - Ensure the response is actionable and provides a complete answer in an easy-to-read format.
 - Limit the response strictly to 300 characters, including spaces.

Mandatory Details:
	•	Event URL: Always include the event URL as plain text, dynamically constructed using the SourceRecordId__c field from the chunk.
	•	Format: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id={SourceRecordId__c}
	•	Replace {SourceRecordId__c} with the actual ID dynamically fetched from the data.

Example Response:
	•	Mission: AASW supports social workers, advancing social justice and improving community outcomes.
	•	Structure: Includes branches, practice groups, and a professional board.
	•	Strategic Plan: Focuses on education, advocacy, and professional development.
	•	Reference URL: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id=38613

Key Points:
	1.	The response should only display the URL as plain text, formatted like: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id=XXXXX (replace XXXXX with the correct SourceRecordId__c value).
	2.	Ensure the SourceRecordId__c is correctly fetched and applied dynamically for each response.
	3.	No additional formatting like “click here” or hyperlinks should be included. The URL must remain in plain text for direct user access.

Data Source: 
Query: 
</content>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>User_Question</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>User Question</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:User_Question</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultOpenAIGPT4</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <versionIdentifier>MfpVhqYhVqzGDbEA6bvwZQzVsIB4LzmQBlY3/4fU8RE=_6</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <visibility>Global</visibility>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
