<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPromptTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <activeVersion>MfpVhqYhVqzGDbEA6bvwZQzVsIB4LzmQBlY3/4fU8RE=_7</activeVersion>
    <createdInVersion>62.0</createdInVersion>
    <description>This is a prompt for the about us Section of AASW website</description>
    <developerName>AASW_AboutUs</developerName>
    <masterLabel>AASW_AboutUs</masterLabel>
    <templateVersions>
        <content>Generate a concise, user-friendly response about the Australian Association of Social Workers (AASW), including details about its mission, vision, structure, history, strategic plan, branches, practice groups, and board of directors. Ensure the URL is presented as the last point in the specified format.

Instructions

Content Focus:
	1.	Address key topics about AASW, such as:
	•	Mission: Highlight AASW’s commitment to supporting social workers and promoting social justice.
	•	Vision: Detail its long-term goals for advancing the social work profession.
	•	Structure: Mention its branches, practice groups, and board of directors.
	•	Strategic Plan: Summarize the 2024-2027 plan with its primary goals and initiatives.
	•	History: Include a brief note on its foundation and achievements.
	2.	Include key organizational information:
	•	Constitution and Bylaws.
	•	Membership categories and roles.

Language and Presentation:
	•	Use professional, straightforward language.
	•	Organize the response using bullet points for clarity.
	•	Ensure the response is concise and does not exceed 300 characters, including spaces.

Mandatory Details:
	•	Event URL: Always include the event URL as plain text, dynamically constructed using the SourceRecordId__c field from the chunk.
	•	Format: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id={SourceRecordId__c}
	•	Replace {SourceRecordId__c} with the actual ID dynamically fetched from the data.

Example Response:
	•	Mission: AASW supports social workers, advancing social justice and improving community outcomes.
	•	Structure: Includes branches, practice groups, and a professional board.
	•	Strategic Plan: Focuses on education, advocacy, and professional development.
	•	Reference URL: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id=38613

Key Points:
	1.	The response should only display the URL as plain text, formatted like: https://www.aasw.asn.au/?page_id=XXXXX (replace XXXXX with the correct SourceRecordId__c value).
	2.	Ensure the SourceRecordId__c is correctly fetched and applied dynamically for each response.
	3.	No additional formatting like “click here” or hyperlinks should be included. The URL must remain in plain text for direct user access.

Data Source: {!$EinsteinSearch:Default_Trasformed_POSTPAGE_DMO_Retriever_1Cx_SE151488ab2.results}
Query: {!$Input:User_Question}
</content>
        <inputs>
            <apiName>User_Question</apiName>
            <definition>primitive://String</definition>
            <masterLabel>User Question</masterLabel>
            <referenceName>Input:User_Question</referenceName>
            <required>true</required>
        </inputs>
        <primaryModel>sfdc_ai__DefaultOpenAIGPT4_32k</primaryModel>
        <status>Published</status>
        <templateDataProviders>
            <definition>invocable://getEinsteinRetrieverResults/Default_Trasformed_POSTPAGE_DMO_Retriever_1Cx_SE151488ab2</definition>
            <parameters>
                <definition>primitive://String</definition>
                <isRequired>true</isRequired>
                <parameterName>searchText</parameterName>
                <valueExpression>{!$Input:User_Question}</valueExpression>
            </parameters>
            <referenceName>EinsteinSearch:Default_Trasformed_POSTPAGE_DMO_Retriever_1Cx_SE151488ab2</referenceName>
        </templateDataProviders>
        <versionIdentifier>MfpVhqYhVqzGDbEA6bvwZQzVsIB4LzmQBlY3/4fU8RE=_7</versionIdentifier>
    </templateVersions>
    <type>einstein_gpt__flex</type>
    <visibility>Global</visibility>
</GenAiPromptTemplate>
